way2success.com 2015-04-29

# Privacy-Policy

### Privacy Policy

Way2success has created this privacy policy as part of our commitment to maintain customer privacy and a clean business environment. 

By access and use of this website you accept and agree to be bound by the legal terms of use. By this we mean that you have agreed to be bound by our terms and conditions and if you are acting on behalf of some company or other entity you possess the capacity to bind such company or entity to us.

We recognize that by providing us with your personal information you are demonstrating you trust in our company and this is a very serious matter with us. We have gathered this information to process your needs and enquiries and maintain any correspondences with you. 

Way2success also reserves the right to Transfer your information to our service providers to administer and provide services on our behalf. We bind these service providers – individual or organization to use your information only for the processing of services and for no other purpose.

If you choose to provide personal information to way2success we assume that you consent to the collection use and disclosure of your personal information as described at the time of collection and as outlined in this Privacy Statement. Your consent may be express or implied depending on the circumstances and the sensitivity of the personal information in question. If you do not consent please do not provide your personal information or where applicable exercise the opt-in or opt-out options offered. Subject to legal and contractual requirements and reasonable notice you may refuse to consent to our collection use and disclosure of your personal information.

Way2success may collect certain information from visitors to and clients of the site such as Internet information like IP Addresses. This information is logged to diagnose any technical difficulties, to administer the confidentiality of our website, and to improve the quality of our services.   
We may track and analyze any non-identifiable and aggregate usage statistical information and provide this to a third party to improve our service quality.

**Misuse of Website (by any visitor)**  
Any misuse of our website in the form of any malware or spyware is a serious offence and can be subject to legal penalties apart from non-availability of the use of services of our website.

**Cookies**  
From time to time we may set up websites in support of specific promotions. When you view one of our websites or online advertisements or promotions we may store some information on your computer in the form of "cookies" or similar files. This information stored on your computer's hard drive does not contain any personal information, but enables us to communicate more meaningfully with you. These cookies also enable you to use our website more efficiently by storing your login information. With most Internet Browsers you can erase cookies from your hard drive block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or Help screen to learn more about these functions. As most Websites do however, we do track usage patterns on our Website on an anonymous basis. Your identity cannot reasonably be ascertained from this information. Each time you visit our Website our server records your Internet Service Provider the date and time of your visit the pages you visit and the documents downloaded the searches you performed and the referring URL's you came from. We use this non-personal information to optimize our Website service.

**Log files**  
Way2success maintains log files of the traffic that visits our site. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personally identifying information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads and information technology requirements for providing reliable service. Information collected includes IP addresses and browser types. 

**Security of your Information**  
We try to maintain your information security with us by avoiding any kind of mishandling of information. We follow the generally accepted Terms & Conditions to maintain your privacy. However, in any case of discrepancy, we are not liable for any legal channels.

**Change to this Privacy Statement**  
Way2success reserves the right to change, alter, delete or modify this statement at any point of time, so please keep reviewing the website to keep updated on our Policies.

If you have any queries regarding the above policies, you can contact us anytime at: [info@way2success.com](mailto:info@way2success.com)
